

52, 11th Main, 30th Cross Banashankari 2nd Stage Bengaluru, INDIA 560070 ▼ WHC9+8C BSK

- **%** +91 97398 56528
- ઢ varungupta3009

# Experience



**Corporate Operations Engineer II** 

Google

May 2023 – Present (1 mo)

**Corporate Operations Engineer** 

Jan 2022 - May 2023 (1 yr 5 mos)

**IT Resident** 

Aug 2021 - Jan 2022 (6 mos)

**Data and Reporting Analyst Hewlett Packard Enterprise** Feb 2021 - Aug 2021 (7 mos)



Lead in Network Security and Web Development

Developer Student Clubs • PES University Jan 2019 – Sep 2020 (1 yr 9 mos)



Software Engineer

Mindtree

Jul 2019 - Feb 2020 (8 mos)

## Education



**PES University** 

Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science & Engineering 2017 - 2021



R. V. PU College

K-PUC (CS), Affiliated to NCERT, New Delhi



Carmel School, Padmanabhanagar

ICSE, New Delhi — SSLC, Karnataka 2002 – 2015

# **Publications & Awards**

Twitter Spam Review Detection Using Hybrid Machine Learning Techniques Springer, November 2021, ISBN: 978-981-16-3690-5

Software Implementation of an Automatic Movable Road Barrier

IEEE, October 2019, ISBN: 978-1-7281-1576-4

Prof. C N R Rao Merit Scholarship

PES University, November 2019

## Languages

हिंदी (Hindi) English ಕನ್ನಡ (Kannada) **Hobbies** 

Reading

 (- <b>-</b> -	mir	Ω.
uа	mir	12
		ъ.

|--|

	ısic

# Knowledge and Skills

<b>Python 3</b> Experience Skill	
<b>JavaScript</b> Experience Skill	
<b>C/C++</b> Experience Skill	

#### Experience

Windows 7/8/10

Skill

## Frontend Design and Development

Experience •

#### **Full-Stack Web Development**

Experience Skill

#### Angular (TS), React (JS/TS)

Experience Skill

#### WordPress, CMS

Experience Skill

#### Adobe Photoshop & Illustrator

Experience

# Adobe After Effects and Premiere Pro

Experience Skill

#### Blender, Pixar Renderman

Experience Skill

### Cloud Architechture (GCP)

Experience Skill

#### About me

I am an experienced developer with proficiency in web design. Fluent in many computing languages with over 11 years of experience in Python, C++, and JS. Polymath, geek, and love to explore the bleeding edge of technology and internet. I am also a hobbyist designer and hacker.

## Let's Connect

I recommend checking out my LinkedIn Profile to stay regularly updated, and to get in touch with me instantly.

